<resources>
    <string name="signin">Sign In</string>
    <string-array name="locations">
        <item>Bangalore</item>
        <item>Mumbai</item>
        <item>Pune</item>
        <item>Delhi</item>
        <item>Kolkata</item>
        <item>Dhanbad</item>
        <item>Chennai</item>

    </string-array>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment"> <p style="text-align:center;">Identifying unknown attacks is one of the big challenges in network Intrusion Detection Systems (IDSs) research. In the past decades, researchers adopted various machine learning approaches to classify and distinguish anomaly traffic from benign traffic without prior knowledge on the attack signature. Extensive academic research on machine learning made a significant breakthrough in mimicking human brain recently. The state-of-the-art on machine learning breakthrough comes from deep learning which has been predicted to cause a powerful improvement in artificial intelligence field. Numerous complex applications have been accomplished by deep learning. One of the distinguished applications is AlphaGo from Google that uses Convolutional Neural Network. AlphaGo beat the Korean world champion in the “Go” game recently by showing superman-like capabilities in remote machine learning. The advancements on this learning algorithms may improve IDS ability to reach high detection rate and low false alarm rate. However, the deep learning implementations in intrusion detection applications may have some limitations. In this paper, we survey previous IDSs that embrace deep learning approaches. Deep learning methods such as deep belief network, restricted Boltzman machine, deep Boltzman machine, deep neural network, auto encoder, etc., are commonly used in IDSs. We examine such deep learning methods with their advantages and disadvantages in order to get better understanding on how to apply deep learning. We realize that there is a confusion of how to adopt deep learning in IDS application properly. Our claim is that deep learning is useful in IDS, especially for feature extraction. In order to support our claim, we provide future challenges and directions to employ deep learning in IDS accordingly. Finally, deep learning methods can enhance future research on unknown attack detection.
Keywords: anomaly detection, neural network, deep learning, feature extraction. \n\n
        \n  <b><i> <center> <u>1. Introduction</u> </center></i></b>\n
        \nThere are a numerous different type of attacks within cyberspace these days. Comprehensive researches have been executed in order to overcome these attacks. One common countermeasure is to use so called Intrusion Detection System (IDS). An extensive research applying machine learning methods in IDS have been done in both academia and industry. However, the security experts still desire better performance IDS which has highest detection</p></string>
    <string name="app_name">Christ Edtech</string>
    <string name="image_pic">image_text</string>
    <string name="image_desc">image_desc</string>

    <string name="textview_text">The global cyber threat continues to evolve at a rapid pace, with a rising number of data breaches each year. A report by RiskBased Security revealed that a shocking 7.9 billion records have been exposed by data breaches in the first nine months of 2019 alone. This figure is more than double (112%) the number of records exposed in the same period in 2018
        Abstract  Artificial Intelligence is among the most popular terms in the 21st century. But yet not, we can say that AI has been completely developed. AI is still growing day by day in multiple ways. Earlier, AI was used to create technologies that are used to be based on Human Intelligence. AI used to work in the technologies which mainly deal with How human beings used to think, remember, work and make decisions in any particular scenario. And this is one of the reasons we used to say that Artificial Intelligence is the computerized vision of human Intelligence. But as the day passes AI overpowers us, humans, in many aspects. The amount in which modern technology is getting updated daily, its speed, and knowledge can not be handled by humans alone. With more data, information gets increases, which is becoming the need of modern-day business no matter what. From a student to a politician to a businessman, everybody and everywhere, it is the data and its information that is making a substantial impact on us and on our future generation.
    With the increase in information, its security should be one of the significant concerns we should focus on. Cybersecurity mainly deals with the protection of data, and maintaining its privacy, is becoming the critical factor in which any organization is ready to put its best effort in order to protect its information. The ever-expanding of data breaches, cybercrimes, and malware attacks has grown like never before with the increase in the data we are creating every day. Cybersecurity has become an essential part of our lives, and to develop a software system with standard suitable algorithms"
 </string>
    <string name="textview_4">THANK YOU</string>
    <string name="textview_heading">Cyber Security</string>
    <string name="aboutustext"> The Dream app is created for CAC2 Component. I tried to make and Edtech app.
    Although we have faced few problem in the present KP of College And the design is also not so good . At least
    this is what I felt. So I tried to create a basic app which can be implemented in the college if Supervisors
    want it to implement. I SANDEEP SUTRADHAR will be happy to offer my service to my Institution.</string>
</resources>